Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
NETFLIX PRESENTS
It's here.
It's concrete, Lino.
You think you'll go through with a Clio?
What? No, no...
Whose fault is it if we're here?
There must be another way to get 10,000.
We go through this window,
take everything we can and get out.
I'll find another way to get their money.
I need weight in the front.
Your car won't hold, Lino.
Seatbelt.
Shit.
Fuck, it's stuck!
I can't.
Get lost.
Get lost!
Lino, move!
Come on! Fuck!
Fuck.
I've got it!
Come on, let's go!
Come on, throw it!
Behind! Moron!
Turn! Come here. Yeah!
I'm glad you're here.
Don't start.
Which one is it?
That one.
Let go of me!
Come on!
That guy...
You, get lost.
...went through four layers of concrete.
Look! Get out!
He did it with a Clio.
He barely twisted his wrist.
I don't care.
You want to stop that trafficking,
then leave him to me.
The judge agreed.
Come on!
You can't get a guy who's not in jail?
No.
I need a magician. And that's what he is.
Trust me.
Okay, you have one month. No more.
Bring me two chairs, please?
I lead a team of anti-go fast.
-I don't do go fast.
-I know.
-Look.
-That's not me.
I know.
Take it.
My cars are not up to the task.
Zero power.
Zero durability.
Zero chance.
What's your car?
A Renault 21, 2 L Turbo. Don't laugh!
It's the first interception car
used by the force.
I know. My father had one.
What do you want? A good tow truck driver?
No, I'd rather a good mechanic.
With no plans
for the next couple of years.
What does that mean?
I'm done watching my teams
get crushed like hedgehogs.
I want to stop these fucking dealers.
I have the best pilots.
You'll give them the best cars.
Are you serious?
Don't get shot tonight.
I'm picking you up at 7. Sharp.
NATIONAL POLICE
Grey BMW, Adolph, Romeo, Sierra, 7-6-2,
on the run.
We're chasing it, guys!
Interception 10-2. Eyes on the BMW.
Go fast confirmed.
Roger that.
I'm on it.
Forget about it, Areski. Julia is on it.
That's good.
Stop it.
Don't let him go. Get him, now.
No, no!
Block the traffic.
So who's the boss?
We were on it, damn it.
Heading to Paris?
Hey.
That's a beauty.
Show me.
Holy fuck.
Jeff! You called for the 300's spoiler?
Jeff!
-What?
-The spoiler?
I've been waiting for months.
It will get there on the 21st.
Or we have to order--
Julia.
What are you doing?
Nothing, I was in the way.
That's right.
So you go back under your car.
-Charas.
-What?
Can I stay here tonight?
Again?
Okay, I'll call the prison.
But tomorrow morning,
you go back to your cell.
-So?
-We crushed them.
-How much?
-Frontal, 85.
-Peak speed?
-One hundred and fifty.
I can optimize the mass transfer.
You're a pain with your stuff.
You'll get us killed.
Jeff, let's put it on the bridge.
We'll go celebrate. You join us?
No.
Relax, Julia will get there.
I'm not worried about Julia.
What's your deal?
I just risked my life for you.
In six months, not one go fast beat us.
You know it's a lie.
For each go fast we get,
how many pounds do we miss, 400, 600?
They sacrifice entire loads.
They feed us, and we eat.
I'm sure they have intel on us.
Who are you talking about? Who's "they"?
I'll know soon.
You overestimate the opponent.
You won that war, Charas.
And it's a little thanks to me.
If you change your mind, join us.
Can I talk to you?
No.
Jeff, you join us for a drink?
See you Monday, Lino.
You have to stop that!
Come on, get in.
All I say is that you have a vintage car
and you won't let me take a look.
Nobody touches my 2 L Turbo.
-Look at it.
-I'm a pro
when it comes to mechanics, all right?
Just one--
I said no. Never. So stop, now.
Then go faster.
If I'm not in my cell by 8,
-they'll be on my case.
-Relax.
I make the rules.
Today, we'll stray a bit.
You like it?
Welcome to our future garage, Lino.
You should see your face.
Wait.
The best is that.
That's a joke?
Starting next week.
Moss validated that?
In person.
Don't mess with me, Charas.
Don't get excited. It's an early release
but there's some conditions.
And you deserve it.
This is also thanks to you.
You should tell the others.
An inmate in the team,
it didn't look good, is that it?
You've been working for nine months
without even a thanks.
I believe in second chances.
You put too much trust in people,
but don't change a thing.
Oh, here...
Speaking of trust...
I found that in yesterday's go fast.
Can you tell me more about that?
-It's an injection diverter.
-Yeah.
Your engine gets 300 percent power
but it only lasts 650 feet
before it explodes.
Last time I saw that, it was on a Clio
that ended up in a jewelry store.
It's exactly the same.
And?
You were not alone that night.
Don't ask me that, Charas.
He's my baby brother.
I'm not after him.
I'm sure he's working for the guys I want.
Quentin is not a brain,
he just attracts shit.
How long before your Quentin
ends up behind the wheels
of a car that finishes
in Areski's radiator?
Give me your word.
You have it.
-You're sure he's here?
-No.
-We're waiting for Areski.
-He doesn't answer.
I give you two minutes.
Fuck, Areski. Answer your phone.
I'm with Lino. It could go wrong.
Call me back.
Fuck that shit.
Surprise!
You're into maps?
Stop that shit, you need to move, bro.
First, you give me a hug...
Lino, give me your number. I'll call you.
Hey.
Looking for something?
I came to see my brother.
Your brother is busy.
Come back another time.
You can't let him go
for a couple of hours?
We'll get a drink. I'll bring him back.
You told him to come here?
Not at all. Lino, you've got to go.
That's fine, Quentin.
We said we'd hang out, let's do it.
Kad, get him out of here.
What's going on? Hey!
Lino!
Amazing the amount of shit
you can get into in two minutes.
Search him.
Fuck.
I know that beautiful face. Show me...
What's your name?
Lino, go get the car.
Marco. Marco!
Cuff these two.
We'll make them talk.
You brief me?
I'll take care of him.
-No, I've got him.
-See you at the warehouse.
I said I've got him.
-Don't let him take the kid.
-Shut up.
Get in.
We're in deep shit.
"We're in deep shit."
Come on, drive!
Drive!
Charas!
Lino, move! Move, they'll kill you.
They'll fucking kill you. Get lost!
Get out.
Fuck!
Kad, Jacques! You burn it,
you disassemble it. I want it gone!
A phone. I need a phone.
Hey! Don't move!
Put the phone down!
Julia, pick up.
Drop the phone.
Pick up.
Drop it!
Fuck.
Give it.
Pick up.
Search him.
He's clean.
You're Charas' mechanic.
You're not in jail on weekends?
Charas, Bruno here.
They brought me your mechanic.
He was armed. Call me back.
Hey.
Can you call Julia, please?
She's part of the team.
I'll only talk to her.
Okay.
You thought they'd call Julia?
Sit down.
You mind?
Nobody will come, Lino. Sit down.
It's just me.
You were in the car.
Armed men showed up.
You noticed a guy from the junkyard.
He opened fire.
Charas got hit. You couldn't do a thing.
You took his gun and ran to save your ass.
What do you say?
Not bad?
Lino...
I'm trying to save your ass, okay?
I do this for you.
So?
Up to you.
In about 30 min,
they'll find Charas and his car.
We caught you with his gun.
His blood is on you.
And that...
Fuck, Areski. Pick up your phone.
I'm with Lino. It could go wrong.
Call me back.
What's that look?
I've been nice to you.
It's too bad.
Really.
You come with me.
Cop killer.
You got Charas?
Nothing yet.
Fuck.
Bruno, I need your help.
-If they know my mechanic got busted...
-Okay.
Let me do the paperwork.
He's yours in an hour.
One hour?
I can't do better.
Okay.
Nobody gets near him.
I'll make sure of it.
I'll owe you one.
Let's go.
Every time...
Every time, right?
Areski locked the door?
Move!
Get him!
Hold him!
Asshole!
Calm down!
Fill up this form...
Sign here.
-One minute...
-Motherfuckers!
Fucking assholes!
Come here, hurry!
Get out!
What's happening?
François?
Fuck them up, these fucking cops!
Go ahead, fuck him up!
That fucking asshole!
Watch out, behind you!
Go ahead, yeah.
Let go!
Get up!
Come on!
-Let go!
-Get up!
Hold him here!
Cuff him!
Come on!
They lost contact by the river banks.
They shot him like a dog.
He wouldn't get played like that.
Not him.
Lino fooled us all, Moss.
Meanwhile he disappeared.
Ten cops, not one could stop him.
Where were you?
I'm ready to fix this.
Put me in charge.
Charas wouldn't have wanted that,
you know it.
It's gonna be okay.
You're insane! What are you doing?
Now you look like you lost a colleague.
Step up. That shit slows you down.
-What about Moss?
-I'll handle her.
Like you did with Charas.
Fucking shit! Are you kidding me?
I've got the balls to protect us both.
That's how you thank me?
Never say that again, okay?
I won't let Moss fuck this up.
The brigade is ours.
We'll be able to clear double the load.
Without Charas, it's open bar.
You're going too far.
If Lino gets caught...
We'll be the first to know.
You know the guys.
If he talks, nobody will believe him.
He's burned.
I'm not serene.
Why didn't Jacques burn Charas
with his car?
Everything burned.
There is no fucking proof!
Stop being a pussy, shit!
We'll take care of Jacques,
Kad and the kid.
I need you, Marco, okay? Get a grip!
I need you, Marco.
Come on.
Let's go.
Julia!
Hey!
I just want to talk.
-Julia!
-I was framed by Areski.
Hey!
He killed Charas.
I can't turn myself in, I have no proof.
Okay.
You have to believe me.
Fuck!
Julia!
Lino, uncuff me.
You're making it worst.
Charas!
That's not the right rims.
That's not his car.
That's not Charas' car.
Lino, uncuff me!
Lino!
What happened?
I don't fucking know, I was locked up!
-I don't--
-Your story does not make sense.
-I can't--
-You don't listen!
You're not hurt?
That's fine. I got this.
Moss, she's my colleague.
Let her breathe, she'll answer you after.
He threatened you?
No, it was weird.
He did not make sense.
He accused you and Marco.
He's trying to brainwash you.
He was hoping you'd help him run.
-I'd never do that.
-I know, gorgeous.
When they come after you, I'll be there.
Who's gonna come?
Moss...
Colleagues outside.
If they find out about you and Lino...
It's all good, relax.
We won't say a thing, okay?
It wasn't serious between us.
I know.
-Take your time.
-Yeah.
Quentin, don't forget that.
So we cover it?
-Bring it.
-Here.
What the fuck?
The cars are impounded?
You don't need it to track down Lino.
I'll stay for a while, it's such a mess.
It's not necessary.
The team is operational.
There's no more team.
Don't take away the brigade.
Let go.
Why are you calling me?
-Don't make me pay for Charas' mistakes.
-You think I'm here to punish you?
Get that brigade out of your head
and focus on the mechanic.
I'll bring him back.
Be easy on Julia.
Don't make her pay
for her liaison with Lino.
Have a good day.
You fucked up, guys.
Really?
I know you didn't burn Charas' car.
Areski's bullet is still inside.
I'm done.
They're gonna kill him.
Forget about him.
He's not our problem. Drive.
-Let's get the money and the drug.
-That's not the plan.
It will take a minute.
No!
I won't turn myself in.
You're not, I hand you over.
I save your life, and that's it?
I didn't come for you.
I didn't need a thing.
I'm not made for jail.
I took two years for you.
You got out after three weeks.
Where do you think I slept?
And when I was out, I worked for the cops.
Truth is, you never felt better.
When the cop died, I bet you cried.
That cop died because of you.
Never talk about him again, okay?
Sorry.
I'm freaking out.
-I have an idea.
-No need.
-Listen!
-No need!
Fucking listen!
I heard you talk about the car earlier,
with Areski's bullet...
You know where it is?
Yes, I hid it.
Jacques has another hideout.
Areski doesn't know it.
You're just stalling.
Even if I know where it is,
how do I bring it?
I can't take the chance
to run into Areski or Marco.
Not really what I expected.
Let's stay calm.
Listen to me before you make a mistake.
You think you're in charge?
Sorry, I'm out of bullets.
Wait!
The car was not my idea.
Let me go. I'll tell you where it is.
Which car? What are you talking about?
The cop's car.
Jacques did not burn it.
He asked the kid to hide it.
I can take you there.
It's in a barn nearby.
I'm listening.
Julia.
I did what you said.
Given the frame and the steering,
it hasn't run for years.
Lino was right. That's not Charas' car.
-Moss, we need to talk.
-I don't have time!
Lino just made two more victims.
Are you sure it's him?
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
That's not what you think, Moss.
Jeff just told me that--
I really like you, Julia.
But Areski told me about you and Lino.
So you stay put until we find him,
is that clear?
You took your time.
He had a tough skull.
What are you doing?
I'll get rid of the riffle.
You're in a rush?
No.
Get rid of it when we're done with Moss.
He said something?
No more witnesses, no more worries.
Two more and it's over, Marco.
I'm a witness too.
I know what I'm doing.
Find us a quiet spot.
Julia, it's Lino.
Hello?
Give me a good reason
not to hang up on you.
I didn't kill Charas, you know it.
The two corpses at the junkyard,
it's not you?
They were alive when I left them.
Areski and Marco found them, I bet.
Remember where Charas introduced us?
They think I'm your fucking accomplice!
Why am I even talking to you?
Take your car and meet me
where we first met.
Alone.
What are you thinking, Lino--
Go ahead.
I'm Quentin, 19. Abandoned at birth,
I spent my childhood in foster homes,
where I met Lino. He taught me everything.
It's my fault if he's been to jail
and if he goes back.
I was working in a junkyard to pay back
guys I owed money to. Jacques and--
Move on, they're dead.
I was preparing cars for go fast.
Lino arrived this morning
with the other cop.
Charas.
He wanted to take me in
but another cop showed up and shot him.
Areski.
I'd seen him at the junkyard
but I didn't know he was a cop.
Anyway, I've witnessed it all.
Here's how I see things...
You take us in, Areski shoots us before
Quentin testifies. You carry that guilt.
Or you leave with us and we'll come back
together with proof.
What do you say?
You have to be crazy.
Who are these guys?
Go fast organizers.
Lino's old friends.
Fuck.
You go to the farm
and you find me that fucking car.
-Moss!
-What?
My guys apprehended Julia.
She helped Lino escape
in front of witnesses.
Get in.
I have my car.
Don't worry.
I'll wait for forensics,
I'll bring you your car.
Areski!
Coming.
He told me they were dead.
No one's here. Don't worry.
I'm the only one who knows this place.
I'll try to find the key.
No, wait.
Of course. All right...
Quentin!
That's why you brought me here?
Dude, look at all this dough.
What don't you understand? I need the car!
Fuck! We can buy 10,000 cars with this!
Hey!
Quentin.
Hey.
Lino!
I'm just here for the car!
Tell me where it is.
Come help the kid!
Suit yourself.
Tell me where he is!
I'm talking to you. Tell me where he is!
Stop it.
Go get some air.
I've got it, Julia. Fuck, I've got it.
Julia?
Julia won't be able to answer
for quite a while.
Call me directly next time,
it will be faster.
She knows everything.
No one will believe her. You're alone.
I ran into Marco,
we talked about you a bit.
The conversation didn't end well.
You're alone, too, now.
Don't worry about that.
You'll see my new pilots soon.
Charas gone, the brigade is mine.
You're a dead man, Lino.
Funny, you mention Charas.
He left you a souvenir. Want to know what?
Yes, go ahead.
A clue.
It's a car.
-Yeah.
-Red.
With your gun's bullet inside.
You're talking shit.
I got it burned, asshole.
Jacques kept the real one.
Marco didn't tell you?
You don't have the car.
Sound familiar?
Listen to me, you son of a bitch.
We'll find you--
Don't waste gas. I'll bring it over.
Moss will be happy.
You'll never reach the warehouse!
You won't drive 300 feet before I know it.
Listen to me, little shit.
I'll give you one more chance. Run away
from this car if you care about your life.
Charas left me a chance
and I won't let him down, son of a bitch.
The first to catch Lino
gets a spot in the brigade.
I know Charas meant a lot to you.
You're still in shock.
It can help you.
We all make mistakes, under pressure.
Charas had big plans for you
and if he was still around--
If he was still around
he'd be on Lino's side.
You prefer throwing away your career,
your life, for a guy
who could have come clean 20 times
but rather hide?
Sorry, my friend.
He should be here, not you.
He's too busy doing your job.
You have the night to think it through.
Then Internal Affairs will take over,
I won't be able to help you.
And me help you.
When Lino gets back with the car,
you won't be able to say you didn't know.
For sure he'll drive by?
Don't worry, he'll come.
Bring me all the cars!
It's for a movie.
He was located at a gas station.
Say that again.
He's on the D60, coming your way.
Renault 21 confirmed?
Confirmed. Over.
You stick to him so he can't turn around.
Tell me when you see him.
Roger that.
We close the road block.
Okay, 21 confirmed.
He spotted us. We'll pressure him. Over.
Go ahead. You're on.
Come on!
Where is he? I can't see him!
Behind.
Don't slow down!
Stay away from his hooks!
Fucking asshole!
We're down!
Stop, Lino!
Stop!
He's pushing us! Fuck!
Stop shouting, I can't hear a thing.
Fuck! Stop it! He's pushing us!
Stop shouting, I can't hear anything!
Fuck! Don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
Shoot. Fucking shoot!
Go ahead, morons!
Fucking shoot!
Yes, Moss.
Which car was it?
Yes, where?
A Renault 21, red.
He authorized the road block.
We have two casualties, hurry up!
A Renault 21... We're sending two cars.
I don't care that your cars crashed.
Catch Areski.
Going toward the D60.
Areski, pick up. Areski...
I order you to stop the pursuit.
Cars are on the way. If you touch Lino...
No, Julia!
Julia!
Watch out!
I'm near the river banks.
Make sure Areski doesn't get to Lino.
Fuck!
Oh, fuck.
Hey... Julia.
Areski!
Find me anything!
I don't give a fuck, do you hear me?
I need anything, a taxi, an ambulance,
I don't care!
A scooter, who cares?
Move your ass!
I don't know where they are!
Fuck.
Moss!
He's downstairs.
You don't want to give it to him?
No.
Julia...
Tell him to stick around.
In case we need him.